# Adrienne Bills-Chumbley

As a veteran Medical Assistant, I am looking to support a team of health care professionals. A compassionate person that is concern about the quality of patient care.

Lancaster, TX 75134 adriennechumbley@gmail.com 214-641-5671

I have been employed in the medical field for nearly 28 years. I have experience in several areas of patient care, including Dialysis, Pediatrics, Family Practice and Internal Medicine. As a Medical Assistant, I have a sincere interest in helping others and giving patients the best quality of care I can offer.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

## Work Experience

#### **Medical Assistant**

Physical Medicine Consultants - Dallas, TX February 2016 to Present

Triage phone calls, EMR data entry, schedule appointments, vital signs, prescription refills, referrals, charting, submitting lab and special testing forms and retrieve medical records from facilities.

#### **Medical Assistant**

METROCARE BEHAVORAL HEALTH CARE - Dallas, TX November 2015 to January 2016

#### Responsibilities

Vitals, injections, medication refills and prior authorizations, triage phone calls and computer work.

#### **Medical Assistant**

Dallas Internal Medicine - Dallas, TX November 1999 to July 2014

Vitals, ekg,medication refills,referrals, electronic medical records,lab procedures, patient consults, icd-9, ordering procedures, injections, wound care, correspondence and assisting physician.

## **Medical Assistant**

Kaiser Permanente - Dallas, TX June 1996 to November 1999

My responsibilities included performing assessments on pediatric patients. This involved physical exams, vital signs, immunization, prescription call in, sick visits, assisting the doctor with suturing and other procedures.

#### **Medical Assistant**

Medifirst Medical Center - Dallas, TX July 1994 to May 1996

Vitals, DOT physicals,xrays,phlebotomy,charting,medication refills,triage phone calls and assist physicians with sick visits ,injections and sterilize of instruments.

#### **Medical Assistant**

Kiest Park Medical Clinic - Dallas, TX May 1990 to July 1994

Vitals,phlebotomy,papsmears,physical therapy,xrays, medication refills, triage phone calls and charting.

## Education

#### Nursing

Dallas Baptist University - Dallas, TX 1985 to 1987

## Some college. in Nursing, Biology

Dallas Baptist College - Dallas, TX 1984 to 1986

#### **Biology**

Indiana University Northwest - Gary, IN 1980 to 1984

## Skills

Trained in Electronic Medical Records (EMR), X-Ray, Phlebotomy

# Groups

## **Delta Sigma Theta Sorority**

February 1982 to Present

## Additional Information

**Professional References** 

- 1. Barbara Relyea 214-267-0101
- 2. Elizabeth Abraham 214-267-0101
- 3. Stephanie Ybarbo 214-267-0101